scholarshipsandaid.org 2019-06-06

# Privacy Policy | Scholarships and Aid

This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information received and collected by Scholarshipsandaid.org,  and how it is used.

**About our Content**

The content on this site is copyrighted by Scholarshipsandaid.org and any author or user or any 3rd party does not have any right over the same. While most of the programs we publish are openly available online, the content is purely the output of our research team, our content sharing network and the contribution from our members.

**Log Files**  
Like many other Websites, Scholarshipsandaid.org makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

**Google Analytics**

This website uses Google analytics to track the visitors’ geographical location, device being used to access the website, public links being accessed by the user, time duration being spent on the website just with the intentions to provide better performance, content and user experience to the visitors.

**Email and RSS Subscription**

This site allows visitors to sign up for a free updates by providing an email address. The email address you provide is used only to send you the free information, and you can unsubscribe by clicking a link in any issue of the update.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**  
Scholarshipsandaid.org uses cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

**DoubleClick DART Cookie**  
– Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on Scholarshipsandaid.org  
– Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to Scholarshipsandaid.org and other sites on the Internet.  
– Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include Google Adsense.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. Scholarshipsandaid.org’ privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

**External Links**

Scholarshipsandaid.org contains links to other sites. Scholarshipsandaid.organd its owner are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such web sites. Users are advised to verify third party sites linked here for clarification.
